[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionId": 1,
    "question": "I was the first player to have won more than 5 Player of the Month awards in the Premier League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Steven Gerrard", "Gerrard"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionId": 2,
    "question": "I've scored the most Premier League goals in a calendar year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Harry Kane", "Kane"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionId": 3,
    "question": "I'm the leading all-time Scottish goalscorer in Premier League history",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Duncan Ferguson", "Ferguson"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionId": 4,
    "question": "Which player has scored the most headed goals in the Premier League?",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Peter Crouch", "Crouch"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionId": 5,
    "question": "I've scored 5 goals in a single Premier League match in the fastest time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sergio Agüero", "Agüero", "Sergio Aguero", "Aguero"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "questionId": 6,
    "question": "I've made over 50 caps for my country and have made more than 450 appearances in the Premier League.\nI won the Premier League for the first time after playing in the division for more than a decade.\nI was picked as Player of the Season for my club in my 19th Premier League campaign",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gareth Barry", "Barry"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "questionId": 7,
    "question": "I'm the record holder for the most consecutive Premier League appearances",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Brad Friedel", "Friedel"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "questionId": 8,
    "question": "I registered the fastest goal in a Champions League final and made over 900 appearances for one club",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Paolo Maldini", "Maldini"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "questionId": 9,
    "question": "I've scored the fastest Premier League hat-trick.\nThe following year I was named in the PFA Premier League Team of the Year after scoring 13 league goals.\nI've represented my country at the African Cup of Nations.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sadio Mané", "Mané", "Sadio Mane", "Mane"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "questionId": 10,
    "question": "I've scored a hat-trick from set pieces in a single Premier League game.\nI've won the Premier League as many times as I've been named PFA Player of the Month (which is greater than 2).\nMy Premier League career spans over 10 years",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Wayne Rooney", "Rooney"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "questionId": 11,
    "question": "I've scored the most Premier League goals as a substitute.\nDuring my career I've played with the likes of Berbatov, Júlio César, Van Der Vaart & Joleon Lescott",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jermain Defoe", "Defoe"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "questionId": 12,
    "question": "I've scored the most own-goals in a Premier League season.\nI've played on the same team as Pogrebnyak, Keane, Pennant & Glen Johnson",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Martin Škrtel", "Škrtel", "Martin Skrtel", "Skrtel"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "questionId": 13,
    "question": "I still hold the record for the fastest Premier League goal.\nI've been capped for England and featured in the 2010 FIFA World Cup.\nI've played alongside Gallas, Carrick & Robinson during my career",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ledley King", "King"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "questionId": 14,
    "question": "Over 2200 (and counting) penalties have been taken in the history of the Premier League\nI'm the only player who has taken one under the age of 18?",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Michael Owen", "Owen"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "questionId": 15,
    "question": "I made over 300 Premier League appearances all for the same team.\nDuring that time, my club lifted 11 trophies. One of my famous goals was voted the best Premier League goal of all time.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dennis Bergkamp", "Bergkamp"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "questionId": 16,
    "question": "I'm the only player to have scored for seven Premier League clubs?",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Craig Bellamy", "Bellamy"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "questionId": 17,
    "question": "I played for Alex Ferguson, won the Premier League and the Champions League. My team mates included Arteta, Mignolet, Shearer, Klosse, Bale, Rodwell, Adebayor, Duff, Cahill, Drenthe. Who am I?",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Louis Saha", "Saha"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "questionId": 18,
    "question": "I've played both in the Premier League and Championship\nI've played with Lescott at 3 different clubs and with Pienaar and Sinclair at 2 different clubs\nI have a Premier League medal to my name",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jack Rodwell", "Rodwell"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "questionId": 19,
    "question": "I scored my first Premier League goal at the age of 16.\nSome of the names I've been managed by are Allardyce, Rodgers, Mancini & O'Neill",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["James Milner", "Milner"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "questionId": 20,
    "question": "I've got the record for the joint highest Premier League Player of the Season awards.\nDuring one of these seasons I helped my club to a record breaking 14 consecutive games without conceding a goal.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Nemanja Vidić", "Nemanja Vidić", "Nemanja Vidic", "Vidic"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "questionId": 21,
    "question": "I have been relegated from the Premier League 4 times with 3 different clubs.\nI've played for my country (Cameroon) at a World Cup, have been managed by Harry Redknapp and have played in the same team as Defoe and Bale",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sébastien Bassong", "Bassong", "Sebastien Bassong"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "questionId": 22,
    "question": "I've made the most assists in a Premier League season.\nI've never won the League cup but I've won the FA cup, Community Shield and League Title.\nAnother accolade to my name is the European Golden Boot",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Thierry Henry", "Henry"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "questionId": 23,
    "question": "Some of the players I've played with include Phil Jones, Samuel Eto'o, Steven N'Zonzi & Míchel Salgado.\nMy accumulated transfer fee total for my career is in excess of £40 mil",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Christopher Samba", "Samba"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "questionId": 24,
    "question": "I'm a retired striker who has played for a number of clubs which include Chelsea, PSG, Man City & Monaco.\nIn 2018 I will take office after being elected president of my home country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["George Weah", "Weah"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "questionId": 25,
    "question": "I was the top assist provider for one Premier League season, the season after I won the Premier League Golden Boot.\nI've played with Stekelenburg, Dembélé & Taarabt to name a few and have been managed by Sir Alex Ferguson.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dimitar Berbatov", "Berbatov"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "questionId": 26,
    "question": "I've played for both London clubs Chelsea and Tottenham.\nI've never won the league but have lifted the FA cup.\nOne of my career highlights is scoring the winner in a UEFA Super Cup final",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gus Poyet", "Poyet"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "questionId": 27,
    "question": "I've missed the most Premier League penalties in history with 11",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Alan Shearer", "Shearer"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "questionId": 28,
    "question": "I've represented my country at both the Euros and World Cup.\nI was Man of the Match in an FA Cup Final and also have won the Premier League and Champions League.\nI've played with Flamini, Kolo Touré, Coutinho & Aquilani",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Mario Balotelli", "Balotelli"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "questionId": 29,
    "question": "I reached the 100 goal mark in the Premier League without scoring from the penalty spot.\nI played for 5 different Premier League teams but never won the league",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Emile Heskey", "Heskey"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "questionId": 30,
    "question": "My senior career spanned (now retired) over 500 games in which I scored more than 150 goals.\nTeams I have played for include Shanghai Shenhua, PSG, Chelsea, Juventus & Arsenal.\nI've played 50 games at international level, scoring 12 goals and have won the Euros.\nAccumulation of all of my transfer fees equates to over £110mil",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Nicolas Anelka", "Anelka"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "questionId": 31,
    "question": "I'm a joint record holder of the infamous most Premier League red cards in a season.\nI've won all of the three English top flight trophies (PL, FA, LC) and have a Champions League medal.\nSome of the players I have played with include Rose, Berbatov &  Mame Biram Diouf",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Wes Brown", "Brown"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "questionId": 32,
    "question": "I've not won the Premier League but have won the Champions League with an English club having played in defence during the match.\nThe following season the team I played for was relegated",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["José Bosingwa", "Bosingwa", "Jose Bosingwa"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "questionId": 33,
    "question": "Some of the clubs I have played for include Roma, Arsenal and Lille.\nI'm an African Cup of Nations winner.\nPlayers I have played with include Podolski, Ashley Cole & Idrissa Gueye",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gervinho"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "questionId": 34,
    "question": "I'm the all-time leading goalscorer for my country and I've scored a total of 3 hat-tricks in the Premier League.\nI've been managed by Glenn Hoddle & Rafael Benítez and have played in the same side as Cudicini & Ashley Cole",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Robbie Keane", "Keane"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "questionId": 35,
    "question": "I've played for Chelsea and have been managed by the likes of Mourinho & Scolari. My teammates have included Demba Ba, Malouda, Pepe & Arnautović.\nI've won 3 different top flight European domestic leagues",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ricardo Quaresma", "Quaresma"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "questionId": 36,
    "question": "I've scored more Premier League goals than Dennis Bergkamp.\nI've won the Premier League and FA Cup, but not the League Cup.\nI've scored a goal in the Champions League Final.\nSince retiring from playing, I have managed a club in the Premier League, although the team were relegated during my tenure",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ole Gunnar Solskjær", "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer", "Solskjaer"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "questionId": 37,
    "question": "I've scored the most goals in a Premier League season for a relegated club, this also made me the highest scoring Englishman in the league that season.\nI've been managed by David Moyes & Steve McClaren",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Andy Johnson", "Johnson", "Andrew Johnson"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "questionId": 38,
    "question": "I've won the Scottish Premier League with Rangers and have been named African Player of the Year on multiple occasions.\nPele included me in his FIFA 100 - 'greatest living footballers'.\nI've played with Phil Jones & Carragher",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["El Hadji Diouf", "Diouf"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "questionId": 39,
    "question": "I've scored 30 goals or more in a Premier League season which earned me the Golden Boot and also the European Golden Shoe.\nI've been managed by Alex McLeish & Kevin Keegan and have played in the same team as Milan Baros & Djemba-Djemba",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Kevin Phillips", "Phillips"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "questionId": 40,
    "question": "I was born after the Premier League began and I've managed to score a hat-trick in it.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Raheem Sterling", "Sterling"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "questionId": 41,
    "question": "I've scored a hat-trick of headers in a single Premier League match.\nI've played for two different Spanish teams, two different Russian teams and a single English team as part of my career (as of 2018).\nI didn't win La Liga but have lifted the Russian Premier League & Russian Super Cup trophies",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Salomón Rondón", "Rondón", "Salomon Rondon", "Rondon"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "questionId": 42,
    "question": "I've played every minute of a title winning Premier League season.\nI've also won the French League Cup, English League Cup & Europa League.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["César Azpilicueta", "Cesar Azpilicueta", "Azpilicueta", "Dave"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "questionId": 43,
    "question": "I'm the only player to have taken 10 or more penalties in the Premier League and convert them all.\nI've won more than one Premier League title and have lifted the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Yaya Touré", "Touré", "Yaya Toure", "Toure"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "questionId": 44,
    "question": "My goals to game ratio for club and country was above 0.47.\nI've won the Bundesliga golden boot on two occasions without winning the league.\nI've scored hat-trick(s) in the Premier League and the UEFA Cup\nand I've got an African Cup of Nations runners up medal having lost the final on penalties.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Tony Yeboah", "Anthony Yeboah", "Yeboah"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "questionId": 45,
    "question": "I've scored a Premier League penalty with both feet.\nTeams I've played for include Spurs, QPR & West Ham.\nI played Sunday League football for Senrab FC alongside John Terry & Ledley King.\nI've won the Second & Third Division's Golden Boot and made it to England International level",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Bobby Zamora", "Zamora", "Robert Zamora"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "questionId": 46,
    "question": "I've scored a hat-trick in the Premier League, FA Cup and Champions League.\nI've played on the same team as Walcott, Gerrard & Terry during my career.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Yossi Benayoun", "Benayoun"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "questionId": 47,
    "question": "I'm the all-time top goalscorer for my country.\nI've won the Golden Boot in Serie A, Bundesliga, UEFA Europa League and was the joint second highest scorer in the FIFA World Cup 2010 qualifiers.\nIn terms of trophies, I've won the Premier League and the Bundesliga.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Edin Džeko", "Džeko", "Edin Dzeko", "Dzeko"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "questionId": 48,
    "question": "I'm in the Guinness World Records for the longest goal scored in football.\nIt's my only career goal and my only club career accolade is a Premier League title",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Asmir Begović", "Begović", "Asmir Begovic", "Begovic"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "questionId": 49,
    "question": "I've won the Premier League, La Liga, Ligue 1 and the Champions League\nSince retiring I've been an assistant coach in the French and English leagues alonside the same manager\nI've also managed a club but I'm most recognisable from playing with the likes of Zinedine Zidane and Raul to name a few",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Claude Makélélé", "Makélélé", "Claude Makelele", "Makelele"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "questionId": 50,
    "question": "I've been capped internationally for Scotland and have played for two relegated Premier League teams in the same season.\nI've played in all 4 professional domestic England leagues and have made the PFA Team of the Year in League One & Two.\nI've been promoted to the Premier League with two different clubs",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["George Boyd", "Boyd"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "questionId": 51,
    "question": "I'm an attacking player who has played with the likes of Torres, Kalou, Alonso & Keane.\nAfter scoring a hat-trick in the last game of the season to secure my club their first league title in the 21st century I announced my retirement",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dirk Kuyt", "Kuyt", "Dirk Kuijt", "Kuijt"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "questionId": 52,
    "question": "I've played alongside the likes of Messi, Bojan, Robin van Persie & Kolo Toure.\nMy greatest club achievements include a La Liga title and a UEFA Champions League.\nOne season I got the highest assists in the Bundesliga",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Alexander Hleb", "Hleb"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "questionId": 53,
    "question": "I've played in the same team as Sergio Aguero, Gary Medel, Felipe Melo and Radamel Falcao\nI'm a forward still currently playing as of 2018 however, I've have not scored more than 10 goals in a single season since 2012-2013\nI've won the Premier League and League Cup in the same season",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Stevan Jovetić", "Stevan Jovetic", "Jovetić", "Jovetic"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "questionId": 54,
    "question": "I'm a striker who ended up taking more corners than having shots during my time in the Premier League.\nSome of the players I have played with include Nolito, Luis Suárez & Juan Mata.\nI've scored an International goal against England at Wembley.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Iago Aspas", "Aspas"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "questionId": 55,
    "question": "Some of the players I've played with before retiring include Kaka, Claudio Pizarro, Jaap Stam & Nicholas Anelka.\nI won the Ballon d'Or in front of the likes of Ronaldinho and Henry and I'm the top goalscorer for my country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Andriy Shevchenko", "Shevchenko"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "questionId": 56,
    "question": "I'm a goalkeeper, but I've managed to score, assist and win a penalty in the Premier League.\nI've made 5 assists, more than any other keeper.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Paul Robinson", "Robinson"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "questionId": 57,
    "question": "I've played for 15 different clubs during my senior career which I retired from in 2017.\nThey included Chelsea, Tottenham, Monaco & Barcelona.\nI've won the Premier League, La Liga & Champions League and have scored over 100 goals in my career.\nI'm also the current top goalscorer for my country (at 2018), a country which has qualified for the 2018 FIFA World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Eiður Guðjohnsen", "Gudjohnsen", "Eidur Gudjohnsen", "Eiður Smári", "Eidur Smari"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "questionId": 58,
    "question": "During my playing career (now retired), I have been managed by the likes of Souness, Mourinho, Ranieri & Allardyce.\nIn 2002 I made the UEFA Team of the Year which featured the likes of Ronaldo(9), Henry & Zidane",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Damien Duff", "Duff"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "questionId": 59,
    "question": "I'm a French player who was part of the invincibles Arsenal team which famously won the Premier League without being beaten.\nI did not get on the scoresheet during that season.\nFollowing my time at Arsenal, I moved to Spain to play in La Liga",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Pascal Cygan", "Cygan"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "questionId": 60,
    "question": "I have managed to win 2 Premier League medals by only playing a total of 12 matches in total for two different teams.\nThe two teams were Arsenal and Man City",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Richard Wright", "Wright"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "questionId": 61,
    "question": "I'm a Brazilian international who has won a Premier League medal.\nSome players I've played with include Bosingwa, Zaha, & Negredo and I've been managed by Harry Redknapp",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Fábio da Silva", "Fábio", "Fabio da Silva", "Fabio"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "questionId": 62,
    "question": "I've scored hat-tricks against the same club in both matches of a Premier League season.\nI have a Champions League runners up medal with Monaco and a Copa del Rey winners medal with Real Madrid.\nI've played in the same team as Zaha & Toure",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Emmanuel Adebayor", "Adebayor"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "questionId": 63,
    "question": "I've scored, assisted and scored an own goal all in the same Premier League game.\nI retired in 2015 and spent the majority of my career at a North England club making over 350 appearances and scoring over 70 goals.\nWe endured 9 consecutive seasons in the Premier League before being relegated and we haven't made it back since (as 2018)",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Kevin Davies", "Davies"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "questionId": 64,
    "question": "I've won a Fifa Club World Cup beating Chelsea in the final.\nI've been managed by the likes of Pochettino & Valverde. Scolari has managed me for both club and country and I've won the Chinese domestic treble having also made the team of the year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Paulinho"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "questionId": 65,
    "question": "I'm in the top 100 all-time Premier League goalscorers as of 2018.\nI've played on the same team as Robert Huth, Alex Song, Paolo Di Canio & Zola.\nI've been managed by Claudio Ranieri",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Carlton Cole", "Cole"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "questionId": 66,
    "question": "I hold the record for playing the highest number of Premier League games to be substituted off in all of them.\nThe team I was playing for was Liverpool",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Nuri Sahin", "Sahin", "Nuri Şahin", "Sahin"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "questionId": 67,
    "question": "I've represented my country (Brazil) internationally.\nI was signed in a January transfer window and scored a Premier League hat-trick before the end of the same season. The season before I was the top goalscorer in The Eredivisie",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Afonso Alves", "Alves"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "questionId": 68,
    "question": "I retired from playing at the end of the 2016-17 season.\nI was part of the team which won Chelsea's first Premier League trophy in 50 years.\nI was awarded the PFA young player of the year for the previous year.\nPlayers I have played alongside include Robben, Owen, Bellamy & Sidwell",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Scott Parker", "Parker"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "questionId": 69,
    "question": "I'm a midfielder who has won the FA Cup.\nI've been at the same club at the same time as the likes of Ronaldhino, Vito Mannone, Eto'o, Defoe & Victor Moses.\nI've also scored a Premier League hat-trick",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jordi Gómez", "Gómez", "Jordi Gomez", "Gomez"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "questionId": 70,
    "question": "I'm a capped England international and have played on the same team as Freedman, Snodgrass, Mile Jedinak, Christopher Samba and Robert Huth.\nI've won the Premier League and have played matches in both the Championship and Premier League. I'm still playing as of season 2017-2018",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["John Terry", "Terry"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "questionId": 71,
    "question": "I've scored in the Premier League, Championship, League One, League Two, Europa League and Champions League.\nI'm uncapped internationally for my country (England)",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gary Hooper", "Hooper"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "questionId": 72,
    "question": "I've played with Dunne, Figo, Mido & Woodgate at club level./nI've never won the Premier League but have 2 Serie A titles to my name",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Olivier Dacourt", "Dacourt"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "questionId": 73,
    "question": "I've played with Sturridge, Walker, Pirès & Vieira but have not played for Liverpool, Arsenal or Spurs.\nI've played for Man City but have never won the Premier League.\nI'm still a Premier League player (as of 2017-18 season)",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Stephen Ireland", "Ireland"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "questionId": 74,
    "question": "I won the English League Cup during my time in the Premier League.\nPlayers I have played with include Joe Cole, Reyes, Doni & Forlán and I have a FIFA World Cup runners up medal to my name",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Maxi Rodríguez", "Rodríguez", "Maxi Rodriguez", "Rodriguez"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "questionId": 75,
    "question": "Some of the teams I've played for include Leeds United, Crystal Palace, Birmingham City & Chelsea.\nI've played with Drogba, Sebastian Larsson & Cameron Jerome to name a few.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Mikael Forssell", "Forssell"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "questionId": 76,
    "question": "My teammates have included the likes of Ozil, Mustafi, Giroud & Gervinho.\nI've won the FA cup having been named Man of the Match in the final.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Antonio Rüdiger", "Rüdiger", "Antonio Rudiger", "Rudiger"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "questionId": 77,
    "question": "I've scored over 50 Premier League goals with at least 15 of them being headers.\nSome of my teammates have included Lukaku, Matić, & Augero",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Fernando Torres", "Torres"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "questionId": 78,
    "question": "I've won the Premier League on more than one occasion.\nI've had André Villas-Boas & Rafael Benítez as managers and have played with the likes of Maicon & Pedro ",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Oscar"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": false,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "questionId": 79,
    "question": "Some of the Premier League teams I've played for include Crystal Palace, Leicester City, Everton & Wolves.\nOver the course of my career I've scored over 100 goals",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcus Bent", "Bent"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "questionId": 80,
    "question": "I've had 5 seasons in the Premier League managing to score 2 league goals.\nI've played with Owen & Davor Suker to name a couple.\n11 out of the 15 international games I played in ended in a draw.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Igor Bišćan", "Bišćan", "Igor Biscan", "Biscan"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": true,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "questionId": 81,
    "question": "I've made over 375 Premier League appearances but never managed to win the Premier League.\nDuring my career I've played with the likes of Sylvinho, Schmeichel and Crouch",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Shay Given", "Given"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "questionId": 82,
    "question": "My greatest sporting achievement is winning the Premier League, a season in which I made 10 appearances but did not find the net.\nI've played with Huth, Cole and Sheringham",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jérémie Aliadière", "Aliadière", "Jeremie Aliadiere", "Aliadiere"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": false,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": true,
        "FWD": true,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "questionId": 83,
    "question": "I've made over 375 Premier League appearances but never managed to win the Premier League.\nDuring my career I've played with the likes of Sylvinho, Schmeichel and Crouch",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["André Bikey", "Andre Bikey", "Bikey"],
    "clues": {
	    "GK": true,
        "DEF": false,
        "MID": false,
        "FWD": false,
        "RET": true,
	    "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "questionId": 84,
    "question": "I've made over 375 Premier League appearances but never managed to win the Premier League.\nDuring my career I've played with the likes of Sylvinho, Schmeichel and Crouch",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["André Bikey", "Andre Bikey", "Bikey"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "questionId": 85,
    "question": "I've made over 375 Premier League appearances but never managed to win the Premier League.\nDuring my career I've played with the likes of Sylvinho, Schmeichel and Crouch",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["André Bikey", "Andre Bikey", "Bikey"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "questionId": 86,
    "question": "I'm in the top 30 all-time Premier League goalscorers.\nI've played in the same team as Shane Long, Alexis Sánchez & Raul Meireles",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Romelu Lukaku", "Lukaku"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "questionId": 87,
    "question": "I've won both the Championship and Premier League.\nI've played with the likes of Asamoah Gyan, Christian Benteke & Mamadou Sakho",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jeffrey Schlupp", "Schlupp"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "questionId": 88,
    "question": "I've played with Rooney, Evra and Ben Arfa.\nSome of the clubs I've played for include Man United and Anzhi, but I've never won a domestic league title",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gabriel Obertan", "Obertan"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "questionId": 89,
    "question": "I've made over 300 appearances for my Premier League club.\nDuring this time I've won the Premier League, FA Cup and League Cup.\nI've won the Europa League but never the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Antonio Valencia", "Valencia"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "questionId": 90,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League, following up with an FA Cup triumph the following year.\nPlayers I've played with include Aguero, Owen & Savage",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sinama Pongolle", "Pongolle"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "ENG1"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "questionId": 1,
    "question": "I'm the leading World Cup goalscorer of all time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Miroslav Klose", "Klose"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "questionId": 2,
    "question": "I'm the oldest goalscorer in a World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Roger Milla", "Milla"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "questionId": 3,
    "question": "I've scored the most goals in a single World Cup match, which also led me to a Golden Boot in that tournament",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Oleg Salenko", "Salenko"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "questionId": 4,
    "question": "I have a well-known Nike football boot made after of me.\nSome say I'm the true greatest for my namesake",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ronaldo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "questionId": 5,
    "question": "I scored a legitimate goal which was incorrectly ruled out even though the ball crossed the line during World Cup 2010",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Frank Lampard", "Lampard"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "questionId": 6,
    "question": "I'm the second youngest player to score in a World Cup after Pelé.\nThe same World Cup I went on to lift the trophy",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Kylian Mbappé", "Mbappé", "Kylian Mbappe", "Mbappe"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "questionId": 7,
    "question": "During a World Cup winning campaign I played in every match and did not register a single shot on goal.\nWith that being said, I'm actually in the top 5 of all-time leading goalscorers for my country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Olivier Giroud", "Giroud"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "questionId": 8,
    "question": "Some of my accolades include winning the Premier League and FA Cup.\nUnfortuantely I'm well known for a penalty miss that assisted in my country being knocked out of a World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Paul Ince", "Ince"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "questionId": 9,
    "question": "I'm the joint record holder for the most number of clean sheets in World Cup history.\nI won the World Cup in my inaugural appearence and was a runner-up 8 years later having played in the final of both",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Fabien Barthez", "Barthez"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "questionId": 10,
    "question": "I have the achievement for making the highest number of caps for my country.\nThis is coupled with the record of making the most appearances for club and country of all time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Peter Shilton", "Shilton"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "questionId": 11,
    "question": "I'm arguably the greatest player of all time.\nA big influence of this is due to me having won the most World Cups of any player",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Pelé", "Pele"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "questionId": 12,
    "question": "I've participated in 4 World Cups and I'm my country's leading goalscorer.\nI'm known for my goalscoring ability, yet I only managed 3 goals during my World Cup appearences",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Samuel Eto'o", "Eto'o", "Eto", "Samuel Eto"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "questionId": 13,
    "question": "I've lifted the World Cup on one occasion.\nI'm currently my country's leading goalscorer which includes 9 goals in the World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["David Villa", "Villa"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "questionId": 14,
    "question": "I'm a German footballer and have the record for playing the highest number of World Cup matches of all time.",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Lothar Matthäus", "Lothar Matthaus", "Matthäus", "Matthaus"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "questionId": 15,
    "question": "I've been to 3 World Cups.\nMy most notable moment was a wonder goal I scored during the 2006 World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Joe Cole", "Cole"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "questionId": 16,
    "question": "I've won the Euros during my international career but have never managed to win the World Cup.\nMy brother is also a well known footballer and although he has never won an international trophy, he is deemed the better player of us two",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Brian Laudrup", "Laudrup"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "questionId": 17,
    "question": "After a successful footballing career which included winning a World Cup after scoring a penalty in the final, my career is now in politics",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Romário", "Romario"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "questionId": 18,
    "question": "Although I've won 8 top division domestic league titles and a Champions League, winning the World Cup may just be my greatest achievement.\nI've been included in 3 separate World Cup's All-Star teams",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Philipp Lahm", "Lahm"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "questionId": 19,
    "question": "I've scored the winning goal in a World Cup final.\n I've also ben named in the Team of the Tournament in a Euros, a tournament in which I was man of the match in 3 of the games",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Andrés Iniesta", "Iniesta"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "questionId": 20,
    "question": "I've won the Golden Boot but have never won the World Cup nor have I won the league at club level",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Harry Kane", "Kane"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "questionId": 21,
    "question": "A goal I've scored in a World Cup is still mentioned today.\nThe team it was against included Nelson Vivas",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Michael Owen", "Owen"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "questionId": 22,
    "question": "I've scored the first goal in a World Cup, of which was my home nations World Cup.\nI've played in the Turkish top division and have also played for a team which has a similar name to a famous band",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Siphiwe Tshabalala", "Tshabalala"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "questionId": 23,
    "question": "I've played in the Premier League, Bundesliga and Serie A.\nMy most memorable moment in a World Cup is scoring a hat-trick",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Xherdan Shaqiri", "Shaqiri"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "questionId": 24,
    "question": "Some of the names I've been managed by include Pellegrini and Sarri.\nI've scored a hat-trick in a World Cup and have played in Serie A, Premier League and La Liga during my club career",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gonzalo Higuaín", "Higuaín", "Gonzalo Higuain", "Higuain"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "questionId": 25,
    "question": "I've captained a side which went unbeaten in a World Cup.\nPlayers I've played with during my career include Gareth Bale & Louis Saha",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ryan Nelsen", "Nelsen"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "questionId": 26,
    "question": "I'm the only player to have appeared in 3 consecutive World Cup finals",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Cafu"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "questionId": 27,
    "question": "I played every minute of every match as I captained my national team to a World Cup trophy.\nWe managed to concede only 2 goals throughout the entire tournament.\nIt was these performances which played a part in me securing the Ballon d'Or that same year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Fabio Cannavaro", "Cannavaro"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "questionId": 28,
    "question": "I've scored more than 8 World Cup goals.\n5 of which came in a single World Cup.\nAn interesting fact is that I've scored the milestone 2,000th goal for my country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Thomas Müller", "Müller", "Thomas Muller", "Muller"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "questionId": 29,
    "question": "I'm the most capped player for my country.\nI'm a World Cup winner and am the only player in my position to have won the Golden Foot award",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gianluigi Buffon", "Gigi Buffon", "Buffon"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "questionId": 30,
    "question": "I won the World Cup and then the European Championship two years later.\nI've played at the top level domestically for France, Italy and Spain.\nI've made over 140 caps for my country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Lilian Thuram", "Thuram"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "questionId": 31,
    "question": "I've never won the World Cup, but I have come close having won a runners-up medal.\nTeams I've played for in the past include A.C Milan, Ajax and Real Madrid",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Klaas-Jan Huntelaar", "Huntelaar"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "questionId": 32,
    "question": "I've scored over 300 goals for club and country combined.\nI've won the World Cup and have continued in the game as a manager.\nMy entire career has been spent in just the one country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Filippo Inzaghi", "Inzaghi"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "questionId": 33,
    "question": "I'm in the top 30 all-time leading goalscorers in World Cup history with a goals per game of over 1 goal in every 2 games.\nI'm also my country's leading goalscorer.\nOther accolades include winning an English League Cup and the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Luis Suárez", "Suárez"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "questionId": 34,
    "question": "I've scored the fastest brace in a World Cup.\nYet I've only scored a total of 3 World Cup goals.\nMy brace was scored in the tournament we went on to win",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Toni Kroos", "Kroos"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "questionId": 35,
    "question": "I've missed the most penalties (excl. shoot-outs) during a World Cup.\nDuring my career I've played in Italy, England, France and China",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Asamoah Gyan", "Gyan"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "questionId": 36,
    "question": "In a single World Cup I managed to score in every group match, the Round of 16 and the Quarter-finals.\nThat's 5 consecutive World Cup matches",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["James Rodríguez", "Rodríguez", "James Rodriguez", "Rodriguez"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "questionId": 37,
    "question": "I'm infamously the first player to receive two red cards in World Cup history.\nI'm a multiple time African Cup of Nations winner and have played with the likes of Steven Gerrard and Paolo Di Canio at club level",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Rigobert Song", "Rigobert Song"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "questionId": 38,
    "question": "I converted arguably the best team goal in World Cup history, which involved 24 passes in the build up",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Esteban Cambiasso", "Cambiasso"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "questionId": 39,
    "question": "During a World Cup, I opened the scoring by netting an own goal which subsequently was the first own goal scored by my country in a World Cup.\nI've made the FIFA World Cup Dream Team on two occassions",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcelo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "questionId": 40,
    "question": "I've made at least one assist in the most number of World Cups than anyone else.\nI've also won the FIFA World Cup Golden Ball but, have never managed to lift the World Cup trophy itself",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Lionel Messi", "Messi"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "questionId": 41,
    "question": "I've played every minute of a World Cup winning campaign. This topped off a year in which I also won the Champions League, a feat which had only been achieved by 3 other players at the time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Raphaël Varane", "Varane", "Raphael Varane"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "questionId": 42,
    "question": "I've had the honour of representing my country as both a player and manager at a FIFA World Cup.\nIt was as a player I experienced the most success having won the tournament",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dunga"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "questionId": 43,
    "question": "I'm one of only a few players to make the All-Star Team for a World Cup for my country, albeit for a tournament we got knocked out in the quarter-finals in.\nIt was a tournament I scored my only international senior goal in a career spanning over 10 years",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sol Campbell", "Campbell"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "questionId": 44,
    "question": "I've only played in 2 World Cups but I've made more appearences as a substitute than anyone else in World Cup history.\nThese appearances took me to a World Cup winners and runners-up medal, during the winning campaign I was a substitute in every game, playing only a minute in the final",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Denílson", "Denilson"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "questionId": 45,
    "question": "I've scored a goal in multiple World Cup finals, which is also the same amount of times I've been sent off in a World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Zinedine Zidane", "Zidane"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "questionId": 46,
    "question": "I've covered the most amount of distance in a World Cup having played the maximum number of games available during it.\nI'm in the top 5 all-time leading goalscorers for my country and currently top out of all the players still to be playing",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ivan Perišić", "Perišić", "Ivan Perisic", "Perisic"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "questionId": 47,
    "question": "I made the most crosses in the 2018 FIFA World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Kieran Trippier", "Trippier"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "questionId": 48,
    "question": "During a World Cup, only Neymar, Griezmann & Ronaldo had more shots on target than me.\nHaving made it to the Quarter-finals, I didn't actually manage to score a goal during the campaign",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcus Berg", "Berg"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "questionId": 49,
    "question": "I infamously have been shown the highest number of cards in World Cup history",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Javier Mascherano", "Mascherano"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "questionId": 50,
    "question": "I've gone a whole World Cup without conceding a goal",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Pascal Zuberbühler", "Zuberbühler", "Pascal Zuberbuhler", "Zuberbuhler"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "questionId": 51,
    "question": "I'm the oldest player to have featured in a World Cup at the age of 45",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Essam El-Hadary", "El-Hadary"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "questionId": 52,
    "question": "I was the highest goalscorer for my country in a World Cup campaign that included us making the Semi-finals.\nMy goals were scored against the USA and Italy, the latter sending the opposition out of the competition",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jung-hwan Ahn", "Ahn"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "questionId": 53,
    "question": "I've won the Golden Ball in a FIFA World Cup.\nThis can be seen as a bigger individual achievement given that my country did not make it to the final",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Diego Forlán", "Forlán", "Diego Forlan", "Forlan"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "questionId": 54,
    "question": "In a successful World Cup campaign which saw my country reach the final, I had racked up an impressive 4 Man of the Match awards in the run-up to it, which is the joint highest in history for a single World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Wesley Sneijder", "Sneijder"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "questionId": 55,
    "question": "I've made the Team of the Tournament in a World Cup before, a tournament in which I made an impressive 27 saves",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Thibaut Courtois", "Courtois"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "questionId": 56,
    "question": "I've played my domestic football in Russia, Portugal & England.\nOne of my biggest individual accolades is making the All-Star Team in a World Cup, referring to the Castrol Index Top 11, I was the only player from my country to be selected",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcos Rojo", "Rojo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "questionId": 57,
    "question": "I'm the only player to have every made the a World Cup All-Star team in my position for my country.\nI also share the record for scoring the most number of goals in a single World Cup for that position",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Yerry Mina", "Mina"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "questionId": 58,
    "question": "During my first World Cup, we happened to win the tournament in which a goal I scored was voted FIFA World Cup Goal of the Tournament",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Benjamin Pavard", "Pavard"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "questionId": 59,
    "question": "I was involved in a World Cup match in which 16 cards were brandished.\nI was lucky to end the game with only a yellow given a headbutt incident",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Luís Figo", "Figo", "Luis Figo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "questionId": 60,
    "question": "I once said 'I have all due respect for Ronaldo, Ronaldinho and Rivaldo, who are fantastic players, but they still have to beat me'",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Oliver Kahn", "Kahn"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "questionId": 61,
    "question": "During a World Cup I was sent home by the manager, this resulted in the team refusing to train the following day in protest.\nI was subsequently given a 18 game ban for my actions but decided to retire from international football",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Nicolas Anelka", "Anelka"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "WC"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "questionId": 1,
    "question": "I'm the leading Champions League goalscorer of all time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ronaldo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "questionId": 2,
    "question": "I've made the most assists of any other player in the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ronaldo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "questionId": 3,
    "question": "I've made the most Champions League appearances of all time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Iker Casillas", "Casillas"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "questionId": 4,
    "question": "I currently hold the record for the most assists in one Champions League season",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["James Milner", "Milner"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "questionId": 5,
    "question": "I have been sent of as many times as anyone else in the Champions League.\nI've also made four assists in one Champions League game",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Zlatan Ibrahimović", "Ibrahimović", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic", "Ibrahimovic"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "questionId": 6,
    "question": "I'm the first player to have been born in the 2000s and to play in the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Moise Kean", "Kean"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "questionId": 7,
    "question": "I'm part of a small club of players that have managed to win the Champions League in consecutive seasons",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcel Desailly", "Desailly"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "questionId": 8,
    "question": "I've scored 5 goals in a single Champions League game.\nOnly Lionel Messi has achieved the same feat",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Luiz Adriano", "Adriano"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "questionId": 9,
    "question": "I hold the record for the highest number of consecutive clean sheets in Champions League games",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jens Lehmann", "Lehmann"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "questionId": 10,
    "question": "I've been shown more yellow cards than any other player in the history of the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sergio Ramos", "Ramos"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "questionId": 11,
    "question": "I've made 4 assists in a single Champions League game.\nThe opposition in that game was Lyon",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Carlos Martins", "Martins"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "questionId": 12,
    "question": "I'm the oldest player to have scored a goal in the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Francesco Totti", "Totti"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "questionId": 13,
    "question": "I've won the FA Cup, Bundesliga, Champions League & have been a finalist in a World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dietmar Hamann", "Hamann"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "questionId": 14,
    "question": "I'm a Champions League winner.\nTeams I have played for include Inter Milan, Arsenal & Man United",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Mikaël Silvestre", "Silvestre", "Mikael Silvestre"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "questionId": 15,
    "question": "I've scored a brace in a Champions League final and was pivotal to my club's treble winning season\n",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Diego Milito", "Milito"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "questionId": 16,
    "question": "I'm in a group of players that have lost both a Champions League and World Cup final in the same year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Dejan Lovren", "Lovren"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "questionId": 17,
    "question": "I'm one of a small group of players that have won the Champions League and World Cup in the same year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sami Khedira", "Khedira"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "questionId": 18,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League on at least 3 occasions.\nI'm part of an elite group of players that have won the treble twice",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sergio Busquets", "Busquets"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "questionId": 19,
    "question": "I was part of a team that overturned a 3-goal deficit in the quarter-finals.\nIncredibly the opposing team was Barcelona",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Alisson Becker", "Becker"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "questionId": 20,
    "question": "I was on the scoresheet in the 2nd leg of a game which saw our club, the first team in Champions League history to qualify after losing the home 1st leg by two goals",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Marcus Rashford", "Rashford"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "questionId": 21,
    "question": "I'm the youngest player to have played in the Champions League at the age of 16.\nA team I have represented in the tournament includes Chelsea",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Celestine Babayaro", "Babayaro"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "questionId": 22,
    "question": "The pinnacle of my playing career has to be winning the Champions League and Euros in the same year",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Juan Mata", "Mata"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "questionId": 23,
    "question": "I'm the first player born in the 2000s to score a goal in the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Jadon Sancho", "Sancho"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "questionId": 24,
    "question": "One of my biggest career accomplishments is winning a Champions League title.\nPlayers I've played with at club level include Chadli, Crouch and Choupo-Moting",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Darren Fletcher", "Fletcher"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "questionId": 25,
    "question": "I've scored the fastest ever Champions League goal",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Roy Makaay", "Makaay"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "questionId": 26,
    "question": "I'm the first player to have assisted a goal in 3 different Champions League finals.\nI'm also the only player to have won Man of the Match in a Champions League, Euros and World Cup final",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Andrés Iniesta", "Iniesta", "Andres Iniesta"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "questionId": 27,
    "question": "I've lost a record 4 Champions League finals",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Patrice Evra", "Evra"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "questionId": 28,
    "question": "I made history by becoming the first player to win the Champions League a year after winning the Europa League.\nI was Man of the Match in the Europa League final and made Team of the Season in the Champions League winning campaign",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ivan Rakitić", "Rakitić", "Ivan Rakitic", "Rakitic"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "questionId": 29,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League having scored a goal in both Quarter-final and Semi-final legs as well as scoring in the Final",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Neymar"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "questionId": 30,
    "question": "I've scored the fastest Champions League hat-trick of all time",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Bafétimbi Gomis", "Gomis", "Bafetimbi Gomis"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "questionId": 31,
    "question": "I've won and lost a Champions League final.\nSome of the players that featured in those finals include Pirlo, Ronaldo & Alonso",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Álvaro Arbeloa", "Arbeloa", "Alvaro Arbeloa"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "questionId": 32,
    "question": "I've made the UEFA Team of the Year on at least 3 occasions.\nBut I've only managed to win the Champions League once",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["David Alaba", "Alaba"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "questionId": 33,
    "question": "Teammates I've played with in the Champions League include Gallas, Morata, Pienaar & Di Maria",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Luka Modrić", "Luka Modric", "Modrić", "Modric"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "questionId": 34,
    "question": "Teams I've played with in the Champions League include Porto, Besiktas & Real Madrid",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Pepe"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "questionId": 35,
    "question": "I made the UEFA Team of the Year in what was my first season playing in the Champions League.\nA teammate during that season was Álvaro Morata",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["N'Golo Kanté", "Kanté", "Kante", "N'Golo Kante"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "questionId": 36,
    "question": "Players I've played with in the Champions League include Sergio Aguero, Kylian Mbappé, Tiemoué Bakayoko & Benjamin Mendy",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Bernardo Silva", "Silva"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "questionId": 37,
    "question": "I'm an FA Cup and Champions League winner having won both on a penalty shootout in consecutive seasons.\nI finished my playing career at Bayern Leverkusen",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Sami Hyypiä", "Hyypiä", "Sami Hyypia", "Hyypia"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "questionId": 38,
    "question": "Some of the teams I've represented in the Champions League include Liverpool, Roma & Milan.\nI've never won the Champions League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Alberto Aquilani", "Aquilani"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "questionId": 39,
    "question": "Players I've played with in the Champions League include Sakho, Balotelli, Sagna & both Touré brothers",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Raheem Sterling", "Sterling"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "questionId": 40,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League with more than one club.\nSamuel Eto'o was a teammate I played with during both of those successful campaigns",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Thiago Motta", "Motta"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "questionId": 41,
    "question": "I'm a Champions League and Europa League winner.\nPlayers I've played with in the past include Alves, Torres, Keita & Lukaku",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Oriol Romeu", "Romeu"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "questionId": 42,
    "question": "I was the first player to win the Champions League with 3 different teams.\nOne of those teams include Real Madrid",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Clarence Seedorf", "Seedorf"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "questionId": 43,
    "question": "I'm a South American player who has played over 90 Champions League games.\nThe teams I achieved this with include Inter, PSG, Ajax & Barcelona",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Maxwell"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "questionId": 44,
    "question": "I've scored a goal in a Champions League final.\nMy teammates throughout my career have included the likes of Berbatov, Falcao, Martial & Torres",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Yannick Carrasco", "Carrasco"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "questionId": 45,
    "question": "I'm part of an elite group who has been the overall top goalscorer in a Champions League season.\nClubs I've played for include Liverpool, Real Madrid & Monaco",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Fernando Morientes", "Morientes"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "questionId": 46,
    "question": "I've opened the scoring in a Champions League final and I've also been a top scorer in a Euros.\nSome of the players I've played with include Shaqiri, Jiménez, Can & Kroos",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Mario Mandžukić", "Mandžukić", "Mario Mandzukic", "Mandzukic"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "questionId": 47,
    "question": "I've scored the highest number of Champions League goals of anyone else from my country",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Wayne Rooney", "Rooney"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "questionId": 48,
    "question": "I've scored 13 Champions League goals in my career.\nTeammates I've played with over the years include Bale, Mascherano & Sol Campbell",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Peter Crouch", "Crouch"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "questionId": 49,
    "question": "I've scored a Champions League hat-trick.\nTeams I've played for include Barcelona and Atlético Madrid.\nI've never won the Champions League but I have won the Europa League",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Arda Turan", "Turan"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "questionId": 50,
    "question": "I've made over 100 Champions League appearances in total, some of the teams to have helped make this up are Real Madrid & PSG.\nI Once was the highest paid player in the world",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["David Beckham", "Beckham"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": true
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "questionId": 50,
    "question": "I've netted a hat-trick in the Champions League against FC Basel.\nSome of my teammates have included Zabaleta, Hernández, Nasri & Wilshere",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Lucas Pérez", "Pérez", "Lucas Perez", "Perez"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "questionId": 51,
    "question": "I'm one of an elite group of players to have won the Champions League, World Cup and Ballon d'Or.\nI was the first to achieve it since the year 2000",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ronaldinho"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "questionId": 52,
    "question": "I've been the highest scoring Brazilian in a Champions League season.\nDuring my mid-twenties I decided to move to a club in China managed by Scolari, a team which included national teammate Paulinho",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Alan", "Alan Carvalho", "Carvalho"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "questionId": 53,
    "question": "I'm part of a treble winning team which includes winning the Champions League.\nPlayers I have played with include Can, Xhaka & Salah",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Xherdan Shaqiri", "Shaqiri"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "questionId": 54,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League on consecutive years.\nI've scored over 10 goals in the competition",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Gerard Piqué", "Piqué", "Gerard Pique", "Pique"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": true,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "questionId": 55,
    "question": "I've lost in the final of both the Champions League and World Cup in the same year.\nAlthough I managed to win the Champions League in my next final, my national team went one worse and finished third at the following World Cup",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Arjen Robben", "Robben"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "questionId": 56,
    "question": "I've won a Champions League having got on the scoresheet in the final.\nSome of my other trophies include an FA Cup and Ligue 1 win",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Vladimír Šmicer", "Šmicer", "Vladimir Smicer", "Smicer"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "questionId": 57,
    "question": "I have a Champions League title to my name and I'm the second most capped player for my country.\nOther titles I've won include the Premier League and La Liga",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Claudio Bravo", "Bravo"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": true,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "questionId": 58,
    "question": "I've won the Champions League and have been a runner up in the FIFA World Cup.\nOther achievements include winning the top-flight Greek, Spanish and Dutch leagues",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Ibrahim Afellay", "Afellay"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "questionId": 59,
    "question": "I'm in the top 10 Champions League goalscorers of all time, but I've never won the competition.\nI've also been included in the Champions League Squad of the Season on at least two occasions",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Robert Lewandowski", "Lewandowski"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": false,
      "FWD": true,
      "RET": false,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "questionId": 60,
    "question": "I've won 6 domestic top-flight titles, but my greatest team achievement quite possibly is winning the Champions League.\nThe furthest I have got with my country in a FIFA World Cup is the Semi-finals",
    "acceptableAnswers": ["Park Ji-sung", "Ji-sung", "Park Jisung", "Jisung", "Ji-sung Park", "Jisung Park"],
    "clues": {
      "GK": false,
      "DEF": false,
      "MID": true,
      "FWD": false,
      "RET": true,
      "ENG": false
    },
    "category": "CL"
  }
]